JULIA DIAS VOLPONI

Galway, Ireland

Email: juliadvolponi@gmail.com LinkedIn - www.linkedin.com/in/julia-volponi GitHub - https://github.com/juliavolponi

PERSONAL PROFILE

Currently studying at Code Institute as Junior Full Stack Software Development with hands-on experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Python. Familiar with API integration through project work. Bringing 3 years of customer support experience, including roles in a café and car insurance company, handling client issues daily. Eager to enter the IT industry to grow, contribute, and gain valuable knowledge and experience.

KEY SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python.

Databases: GoogleSheet API's.Version Control: Heroku, GitHub, Git

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

April 2021 – April 2022 Code Institute

Diploma in Full Stack Software Development

(E-Commerce)

Credit Rated by The University of the West of Scotland

PORTFOLIO PROJECTS

 ContactBook - Contact Book as management tool. GitHub https://github.com/juliavolponi/contactBook.git
Technologies Used - Python , GoogleSheet API's...

2. Harry Potter Quiz- Interactive quiz game. GitHub - https://github.com/juliavolponi/harryPotter_Quiz.git

Technologies Used - HTML5, CSS, JavaScript.

3. Healthy Sugar Club- Designed website. GitHub-https://github.com/juliavolponi/sugar-club.git

Technologies Used - HTML5, CSS.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fev 2023 - Present

Boston Scientific, Galway, Ireland Product Builder

- Adhered to safety practices and quality standards at all times.
- Packaged finished products, labelled boxes and stacked for shipment.
- Met production targets and tight deadlines by collaborating closely with team members.
- Made sure that products were produced on time and are of good quality.

May 2022 - Nov 2022

Brazco Coffee Academy, Galway, Ireland Barista

- Recommended drinks based on solid understanding of individual customer needs and preferences.
- Met production targets and tight deadlines by collaborating closely with team members.
- Made sure that products were produced on time and are of good quality.

Dec 2020 - Fev 2022

Mantovanelli Corretora, Vitoria, Brazil Office Administrator

- Supported office manager with proactive correspondence management, document coordination and customer relations.
- Maintained open communication with customers to foster positive relations and provide updates on issues.
- Coordinated communications, financial processing, registration, recordkeeping
- and other administrative functions.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Currently learning DJango Code skills
- Languages: Fluent Portuguese/Fluent English/Beginner Spanish

INTERESTS

- Slack Forum Channel lead.
- I enjoy listening to tech podcasts to be aware of new changings
- Photography/Gaming/Reading